Archives Organization File Additional records 5956
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Job Descriptions in Selected Industries, Publication (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Job Description - Medical Director for a Large Corporation, Publication (Box 11, Folder 4)
    By A. G. Kammer. July 19, 1951. Item is in English.
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Job Re-Design, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
    By Stephen Griew. Employment of Older Workers No. 1. Item is in English.
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Key Job Comparison Plan, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
    By Life Office Management Association. Personnel Administration Report No. 29. Item is in English.
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Work Study and Collective Agreements in the Metal Industry, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
    By B. Lutz. Union Studies No. 14. Item is in English.
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Labor Costs and International Trade, Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
    By N. Arnold Tolles; Betti C. Goldwasser. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Unit Labor Costs in the Steel Industry, Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
    By Leon Greenberg. April 23, 1963. Item is in English.
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Use of Economic Data in Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 11, Folder 9)
    By Marvin Friedman. Item is in English.
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Labor Education: A Union-University Approach, Publication (Box 11, Folder 10)
    By Jean Hopper. Library Service to Labor Vol. 19, No.1; page 3-8. Item is in English.
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Planning a Local Union Education Program, Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
    By John J. Pearce, Jr.; Irvine L. H. Kerrison. Item is in English.
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Emerging Labor Force, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
    By Seymour L. Wolfbein; Herbert E. Striner. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Americans at Mid-Decade, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
    By U.S. Chamber of Commerce. Series P-23, No. 16. Item is in English.
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: They are America, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: The United States Department of Labor Today, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Labor Force in Wartime America, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    By Clarence D. Long. "Our Economy in War" Occasional Paper 14. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Absorbing the Total Labor Supply, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    By U.S. Chamber of Commerce. "Post-War Readjustments" Bulletin No. 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Woman Power of the Nation Part II, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    By The National Civic Federation. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: America's Next Twenty Years, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    By Peter F. Drucker. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Labor Force in West Virginia: A Study of Its Growth and Characteristics, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    By Edwin W. Hanczaryk. "West Virginia University Business and Economic Studies" Vol. 3, No. 4. Item is in English.
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Chronology of Significant Events in the History of International Trade Unionism, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining and the Labor Press - A Closer Look, Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
    By International Labor Press Assocation. Transcription of a forum. Item is in English.
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Study of Economic Impact of Labor Law Reform Proposal Finds 'Minimal' Probable Effect on National Price Levels, Publication (Box 11, Folder 17)
    By Robert R. Nathan. Item is in English.
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Minutes of Evidence 63, Witness: The Society of Labour Lawyers, Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
    By Royal Commission on Trade Unions and Employers' Associations. Tuesday 13th December 1966, 63rd Meeting. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Minutes of Evidence 35, Witness: Inns of Court Conservative and Unionist Society, Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
    By Royal Commission on Trade Unions and Employers' Associations. Tuesday 26th April 1966; 35th meeting. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Coming Crisis in Labor Law, Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
    By Carroll E. French. Item is in English.
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Union Democracy, Publication (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Bill Analysis, Publication (Box 11, Folder 20)
    By American Enterprise Association. 86th Congress - First Session; Report No. 9; March 14, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Labor Law and Group Ethics, Publication (Box 11, Folder 20)
    By William T. Gossett. Address given by Gossett. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Do We Need Strong Labor Legislation, Publication (Box 11, Folder 20)
    By William Ayres; James Roosevelt; Jim Snyder. Radio broadcast transcript; "The American Forum" Vol. XXII, No. 29; August 18, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Labor Looks at Congress 1959, Publication (Box 11, Folder 20)
    By AFL-CIO; Congress. An AFL-CIO record of the 86th Congress 1st session; An AFL- CIO legislative report publication no. 77-A. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Legal Immunities of Labor Unions, Publication (Box 11, Folder 20)
    By Roscoe Pound. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Outlook for Labor and Social Legislation, Publication (Box 11, Folder 20)
    By John F. Kennedy. October 31, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Labor Law Reform, Publication (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Taft-Hartley Law How It Affects Unions and Workers, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
    By David I. Ashe; George Rifkin. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Analysis of the Taft-Hartley Act, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
    By CIO, Legal Department. Pamphlet No. 153. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Labor-Management Relations Act, 1947, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. NAM Law Digest Vol. IX, No. 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Strange Case of the Taft-Hartley Law, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
    By Claude Robinson. September 30, 1947 issue of LOOK. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: How the New Labor Management Relations Act Affects You as Interpreted by NAM's Industrial Relations Department, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Newspaper (NAM News). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: In the Back, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
    By National Maritime Union of America. Publication No. 17 issued by the Pilot, Education and Publicity Department. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Analysis of the Taft-Hartley Act and Instructions to UAW-CIO Local Unions, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Item 8: Conference of Representatives of National and International Unions, The American Federation of Labor on Provisions of the Taft-Hartley Act, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
    By AFL. July 9, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Amendment of National Labor Relations Act, Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
    By U.S. Congress. Public Law 101 - 80th Congress. Item is in English.
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: If You Were a Congressman, How Would You Have Voted? (Taft-Hartley Act), Publication (Box 11, Folder 22)
    By U.S. Congress. Selections from verbatim testimony on the Taft-Hartley Act before the House Committee on Education and Labor. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Taft-Hartley Act, Publication (Box 11, Folder 22)
    By Princeton University, Industrial Relations Section. Bibliography; Selected References No. 18. Item is in English.
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Under the Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act 1970, Publication (Box 11, Folder 23)
    By Richard I. Johnson. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Under the Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act 1967, Publication (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: Summary of Operations: Labor Management Reporting and Disclosure Act, Publication (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Item 4: Under the Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act 1968, Publication (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Item 5: General Statement Concerning the Election Provisions of the Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of 1959, Publication (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Item 6: Under the Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act 1971, Publication (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Item 7: A Report After Eight Years of the Landrum-Griffin Act, Publication (Box 11, Folder 23)
    By AFL-CIO, Maritime Trades Department. Item is in English.
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Landrum-Griffin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 24)
    By AFL-CIO. Publication no. 111. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Understanding the 1959 Labor Law, Publication (Box 11, Folder 24)
    By Joseph E. Finley. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Strikes, Picketing and Secondary Boycotts Under the Landrum-Griffin Amendments, Publication (Box 11, Folder 24)
    By Guy Farmer. Research Monograph 19. Item is in English.
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Some Aspects of the New Labor Law, Publication (Box 11, Folder 25)
    By Joseph Alton Jenkins. Address given before the Industrial Relations Research Association on October 7, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The New Taft-Hartley Amendments: A Preliminary Look, Publication (Box 11, Folder 25)
    By John H. Fanning. Address given before the New Orleans Chapter Federal Bar Association on October 19, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of 1959, Publication (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The Evolution of the American Labor Market, 1948-80, Publication (Box 11, Folder 26)
    By Richard B. Freeman. NBER Reprint No. 153. Item is in English.
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: The Labor Market and Industrial Relations Research, Publication (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Manpower: The Nation's First Resource, Publication (Box 11, Folder 27)
    By National Planning Association. Planning Pamphlets No. 83. Item is in English.
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Program for Manpower Utilization, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By U.S. Bureau of Manpower Utilization. August 20, 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Mobilization of Manpower, July 1943 - July 1944, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: Projected Manpower Requirements and Supply for the Defense Program, 1951-52, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By U.S. Bureau of Statistics. Manpower Report No. 7; June 1, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Nation's Scientific and Technical Manpower, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By U.S. Bureau of Statistics. Manpower Report No. 3; April 2, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Labor Force, Employment, and Unemployment Annual Estimates By States: 1900-1940, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By John P. Herring. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Fact Book on Manpower, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Item 7: Projected Manpower Requirements and Supply, 1952-1953, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By U.S. Bureau of Statistics. Manpower Report No. 14. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Manpower Requirements of the Machine Tool Industry in the Current Mobilization Program, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics. Manpower Report No. 8; August 20, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Manpower Requirements in the Aircraft Industry, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics. Manpower Report No. 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Labor Today - and Tomorrow, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By James Myers. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Manpower Needs and The Labor Supply, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By Clarence D. Long. No. 442 in the series "National Economic Problems". Item is in English.
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Skilled Workers in American Industries, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
    By Charles S. Slocombe. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Work Will Win: The Story of Manpower, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: Work Will Win: The Story of Manpower, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
    By U.S. War Manpower Commission. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Inventory of Job Seekers Registered at Public Employment Offices April 1960, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
    By U.S. Bureau of Employment Security. August 6, 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Effects of the First Year of the Draft on Employment in the Iron and Steel Industry, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Item 6: Labour Supply and National Defense, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
    By International Labor Office. Taken from the book "Labour Supply and National Defense": 68, 197-201. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Problems of Labor Supply for War Production, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
    By John S. Nagel; Meyer Brown. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Is There Enough Manpower?, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
    By Harold W. Metz. Pamphlet No. 45. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Where Can We Get War Workers?, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
    By Sanford Griffith. Results of a manpower survey in Baltimore; Public Affairs Pamphlets No. 75. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Coming Crisis in Manpower, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
    By Maxwell S. Stewart. Public Affairs Pamphlets No. 68. Item is in English.
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Labor Mobility: Selected References, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
    By U.S. Department of Labor Library. Bibliography. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Labor Mobility: Selected References (Supplement to the April 1967 Edition), Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
    By U.S. Department of Labor Library. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Pink Yo-Yo: Occupational Mobility in Belgrade, ca. 1915-1965, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
    By Eugene A. Hammel. Research Series No. 13. Item is in English.
- Box 11, Folder (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Measurement of Labor Turnover, Publication (Box 11, Folder 31)
    By U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics. Item is in English.
- Box 12, Folder (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Research Planning Memorandum on Labor Mobility, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
    By Gladys L. Palmer. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Mobility and Worker Adaptation to Economic Change in the United States, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. Manpower Research bulletin no. 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Worker Mobility and Skill Utilization in World War II, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Box 12, Folder (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Origin of Antitrust Immunity for Labor Unions, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Box 12, Folder (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Will Labor Fulfill Its Destiny?, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    By Daniel D. Cook. "Industry Week" Vol. 192, No. 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Rediscovering American Labor, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    By Penn Kemble. "LID Looking Forward" No. 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Trouble in the House of Labor, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    By Business Week. Magazine. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The State of Unionism, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    By American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Labor's Long, Hard Road, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    By Air Line Employees Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Role of Labor in a Free Society, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Anchor in the Storm, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    By Edward J. Carlough. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Labor and the Bicentennial: Unions in America, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: The Early Labor Movement in Connecticut 1790-1860, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    By Nelson R. Burr. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: New Directions in European Unionism With Some Implications for American Unions, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    By Everett Kassalow. Item is in English.
- Box 12, Folder (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Brazilian Catholic Labor Movement, Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
    By Howard J. Wiarda. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Assignment '68: A Discussion of the Role of the Labor Press, Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
    By Gus Tyler. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Why Unions?, Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: The Rise of American Labor: From the Beginning, Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
    By Communications Workers of America. Item is in English.
- Box 12, Folder (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The American Labor Heritage, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
    By William L. Abbott. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Labor and the Intellectuals Since 1928; A Bibliography, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
    By Labor and the Intellectuals. Memorandum from Michael O' Prey to Grace Horton dated August 21, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: What's Ahead for Labor Management?, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
    By James J. Healy. From the Sixth Annual R.I.T. Management Seminar, Seventh Session; January 25, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Labor Scrap Book, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
    By United Rubber Workers. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Two Views of American Labor, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
    By Frances Perkins; J. Paul St. Sure. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Labor Movement and Social Change, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
    By Michael Harrington. The first Eugene V. Debs lecture before the Midwest Labor Press Association; Reprint Series No. 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Trade Unions in Britain, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
    By British Information Services. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Trade Union Growth and Recognition, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
    By George Sayes Bain. Research Papers 6. Item is in English.
- Box 12, Folder (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Sweden's Labor Program, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
    By Tage Lindbom. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Labor Looks at Labor, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
    By Paul Jacobs; UAW. Conversation between UAW members and Paul Jacobs. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Labor's Library, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
    By Workers Education Bureau. Bibliography. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Corporation and the Union, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
    By Donald McDonald; J. Irwin Miller; Walter P. Reuther. Interview. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Labor Movement in the United States, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
    By Jack Barbash. Public Affairs Pamphlet No. 262. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Labour Past and Present, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
    By Canadian Labour Congress. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: A Bibliography on Labor in Ghana, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: The Decline of the Labor Movement, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Southern Labor in Wartime, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Box 12, Folder (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Rights in Hungary, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
    By International Labour Office. Studies and Reports No. 50. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Polish Trade Unions Hold Third Congress Will Use All Resources to Speed Improvement in Living Standards and in Work for Peace, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
    By Polish Embassy. Press Release; May 14, 1954; No. 30. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Nonfactory Unionism and Labor Relations, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
    By Van Dusen Kennedy. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Why Unions?, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
    By AFL-CIO. Publication No. 41. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: A Giant's Strength: Some Thoughts on the Constitutional and Legal Position of Trade Unions in England, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
    By Inns of Court Conservative and Unionist Society. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Trade Unions: What They Are, What They Do, Their Structure, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. Trade Union Study Notes No. 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: In Poland Today, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
    By British-Polish Friendship Society. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Labor and the American Way, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
    By Mark Starr. Oxford Social Studies Pamphlets No. 14. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Trade Unions: What They Are, What They Do, Their Structure, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. Trade Union Study Notes No. 1; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Binder of Labour Unions in Michigan, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
    By University of Michigan, Bureau of Industrial Relations. Item is in English.
- Box 12, Folder (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Labor Union Activities and Powers in Major Industrial Countries - United States, Great Britain, Sweden, Germany, Italy, and U.S.S.R., Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
    By Bertha Goss. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Labor Unions in Canada, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
    By A. Andras. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Report on Germany, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
    By Antohny Luchek. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Revision and Correction List to Accompany Directory of Labor Unions in the United States, 1950, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
    By U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics. BLS Bulletin No. 980. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Rift and Realignment in World Labor, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
    By David Dubinsky. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
    By International Labour Office. Third conference of American States Members of the International Labour Organisation report IV. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Directory of Labor Unions in the United States 1950, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
    By U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics. Bulletin No. 980. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Italian Labor Today, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: The Trade Unions and The War, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
    By William Z. Foster. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Citizen's Stake in the Labor Union Problem, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
    By H. W. Prentis, Jr. Address before the General Federation of Women's Clubs on June 19, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Modern Trade Unionism, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: Labor Parties of Latin America, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
    By Robert Alexander. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Trade Union Facts, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 14: Danger Ahead for Organized Labor, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: You and Unions, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
    By Dale Yoder. Item is in English.
- Box 12, Folder (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Salute To the International Association of Machinists, Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
    By Albert J. Hayes; W. Willard Wirtz; John F. Kennedy; Claude Jodoin; George Meany. Addresses to celebrate the 75th Anniversary of the International Association of Machinists on May 5, 1963. Item is in English.
- Box 12, Folder (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: A Survey of Trade Union Members' Attitudes to Some Current Major Social Questions, Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
    By Albert R. Verri. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Union Attitudes Toward University Participation in Labor Education: An Examination and Assessment, Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
    By Harry R. Blaine; Frederick A. Zeller. Reprint Series No. 9. Item is in English.